To go from the periphery to the depth, I already place
表面から深部へと向かうため、私はすでに親指を
my thumbs
私の親指を
in a certain way in the orientation of my ventricles.
ある意味で私の脳室の方向に合わせます。
I make contact first with the texture of the hair.
まず髪の毛の質感に触れます。
And then without really moving, I wait a little bit
そして、ほとんど動かずに、少しだけ待ちます
until I feel the
私が感じるまで
and I feel my hands, you see, warming up a bit, getting...
そして、私の手が少し温かくなり、
getting...
変化し始めます。
There, it's starting to change.
ええ、変化し始めます。
I feel, I feel a difference.
私は感じます、違いを感じます。
Did you feel the moment it appeared?
それが出現する瞬間を感じましたか？
And suddenly, there, it's the bone.
ほら、突然、そこは骨です。
Here, I have a lot of receptors in my hands.
そこには、私の手に多くの受容器があります。
Hello friends, there you go.
やあ、みんな、そうです。
We're going to use them and at the same time, the hand emits heat.
それらを使用し、同時に手は熱を発します。
Now, I'm going to go in very gently.
そこから、私はゆっくりと入っていきます。
I'm going to go from the hair, to the skin, to the fascia, to the bone.
髪の毛から皮膚へ、筋膜へ、そして骨へと進んでいきます。
I'm still on the bone.
私はまだ骨の上にいます。
And now, there, it's starting to pass to the left.
そして今、ほら、それは左へ通り抜け始めます。
I'm gently entering to pass.
私はゆっくりと通り抜けて入っていきます。
I enter, I go into a sensation, a perception, it's
私は入っていきます、感覚、知覚へと向かいます、それは周波数です。
a frequency.
ほら、骨がこのように流動的になり、私はその奥に入っていきます。
There, the bone becomes fluid like that, I
骨は中胚葉であり、中胚葉組織であること、そしてそれは層であることを忘れないでください。
go behind.
脳まで達する層です。
Don't forget that bone is mesoderm, so it's a mesodermal tissue, it's a layer
ほら、私は液体のコンパートメントに到達し、感じ始めます。
that goes all the way to the brain.
私は少し引きます、本当に少し引きます。
There, I'm reaching a liquid compartment, I'm starting to feel it.
より良く跳躍するために、一度引きます。
I'm going to take a step back, I'm really going to take a step back.
ここは本当に表層であり、渦です。
Take a step back to jump better.
Prendre du recul pour mieux sauter.
It's really the superficial layer here, the vortex.
C'est vraiment la couche superficielle ici, le vortex.
Here we see the arachnoid, with the
ここではクモ膜とクモ膜小柱が見えます。
arachnoid pillars.
クモ膜小柱です。
Here I started to have a sensation of the hemispheres.
ここで、私は半球の感覚を感じ始めました。
Now we're going to go a little further.
ここからさらに一歩深く進んでいきます。
And we're going to play with the ventricles.
そして、脳室に働きかけます。
We're going to feel her brain.
その脳を感じていきます。
She just had another sensation, did you feel that?
彼女は今、別の感覚を得ましたね。感じましたか？
Yes, it's like a closing.
はい、閉じるような感覚です。
To show you, I'm going to kind of induce.
お見せするために、少し誘導してみます。
Like a little dolphin, you see on the right, breathing a little less well.
右側に、少し呼吸がしにくい小さなイルカが見えるでしょう。
You just have to give it space.
ただ、彼に空間を与えるだけです。
which will allow it to breathe better.
それが彼がより良く呼吸できるようにします。
I'm coming back out layer by layer.
層ごとに戻っていきます。
That way, it's not straight.
このように、それは歪んでいます。
There, Miss, please describe your perception a little.
さあ、ミス、あなたの知覚を少し説明してください。
At the level, when I really got to the bone,
骨のレベルに本当に到達した時、
I really had this sensation of being impacted.
本当に衝撃を受けたような感覚がありました。
And after, it became...
そしてその後、それは...
it became much lighter, after when
はるかに軽くなりました。その後、あなたが
you went underneath, and the movement
下に入ってから、そしてその動きは
of the hemispheres is very, very, very pleasant, and we could clearly feel the difference between left
半球の動きはとてもとても心地よく、左右の
and right, at the level of the ventricles, and then finally, the frequency
違いを脳室のレベルで感じました。そして最後に、周波数が
which was
でした
more electric, it resembled a very fast vibration, but
より電気的で、非常に速い振動のようでしたが、
not sharp. There, are you guiding yourself on that?
刺すような感じではありませんでした。さあ、それについて、私がガイドしましょうか？